Find out what's possible if you never give up.
Justin Bieber: Never Say Never is a music,
documentary, family film directed by Jon M. Chu.
Tells the story of Justin Bieber, the kid from Canada with the hair, the smile and the voice: It chronicles his unprecedented rise to fame, all the way from busking in the
streets of Stratford, Canada to putting videos on YouTube to selling out Madison Square Garden in New York as the headline act during the My World Tour from 2010.
It features Usher, Scooter Braun, Ludacris, Sean Kingston, Antonio "L.A." Reid, Boyz II Men, Miley Cyrus, Jaden Smith,
Justin's family members and parts of his crew and huge fanbase in a mix of interviews and guest performances.
Self, played by Justin Bieber.
Self - Boyz II Men, played by Nathan Morris.
Self - Boyz II Men, played by Wanya Morris.
Self - Boyz II Men, played by Shawn Stockman.
Self, played by Miley Cyrus.
Self, played by Ludacris.
"Never Say Never" is a song by Canadian singer Justin Bieber.
The song is used as the theme song for the 2010 film The Karate Kid,
and features a rap verse from its star, Jaden Smith.
Originally a risque demo with sexual lyrics performed by Travis Garland, it
was written and produced by The Messengers, and Omarr Rambert.
However, Bieber was tapped to record the song for the film.
He re-wrote the song with the original artists along with Smith and his vocal producer
Kuk Harrell, to feature inspirational lyrics to foil the film's theme.
The song was released for digital download in the United States on June 8, 2010.
The song was later included as an acoustic track on the remix album My Worlds Acoustic (2010) and both the
acoustic and single versions were on the compilation album My Worlds: The Collection (2010).
To promote Bieber's 3D concert film of the same name, the song was released as the lead and
only single from Bieber's second remix album, Never Say Never: The Remixes.
"Never Say Never" peaked within the top twenty in Canada, Norway, and New Zealand, while reaching
the top forty in Australia, as well as charting in other international markets.
After it was re-released as the lead single and the only single from – The Remixes, promoting his film, the single peaked
at number eight on the Billboard Hot 100, becoming Bieber's second top-ten single in the United States.
Its accompanying music video, directed by Honey, features Smith and Bieber in a recording
studio playing around and dancing, and is intercut with scenes from the film.
He has notably performed the song on Today and on his My World Tour.
Smith joined Bieber during the tour's stop at Madison Square Garden to
perform the song for scenes in Justin Bieber: Never Say Never.
The film explores themes of canada, manager,
prayer, pop singer, music competition.